dailyvanity.sg 2019-03-31

# Data Privacy Policy - Daily Vanity

## POLICY APPLICATION

  1. DAILY VANITY (DAILY VANITY Pte Ltd) respects the privacy rights of our customers and we will only track statistics for business purposes. No private information will be disclosed to unrelated entities or any third party merchants unless required by law. All email addresses in our mailing list are strictly kept confidential.
  2. This Privacy Policy applies to personal data collected, stored, disclosed and/or processed by Daily Vanity.
  3. This Policy is based on the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (“PDPA”) and all the associated regulations and guidelines as may from time to time be issued by the Personal Data Protection Commission (“PDPC”) of Singapore. Daily Vanity’s practices may be subjected to different or more restrictive local laws in jurisdictions outside of Singapore.
  4. By visiting or using the Daily Vanity website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully before visiting, using our website, or providing us with any of your personal data.
  5. Information is collected from you when you subscribe to our newsletter; fill out any forms and via cookies. Data that Daily Vanity collects or stores may, subject to applicable law and the PDPA, be transferred to and used by us outside of Singapore. It will be treated according to the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy.
  6. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.
  7. We do not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie.
  8. Please visit Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on to opt-out of this data collection process.

## PERSONAL DATA

  1. It is possible that this website: 
    1. Will use your email to answer queries, process orders, allow access to specific information, receive newsletters, or promotions from us and our partners.
    2. Tracks your usage patterns to serve relevant content or advertisement(s) to you by means of display on website, email, push-notification, and in whatever format that you may have opted-in for via Daily Vanity, our partners, and third party platforms.
    3. Uses remarketing/retargeting methodology with Facebook, Google and Novaly Media to advertise online.
    4. Third-party vendors, including Google, show ads on sites across the Internet.
    5. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to this website.
    6. Data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics may be used to: 
      1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
      2. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
      3. To send periodic emails (The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)
  2. When ordering or registering on our site, personal data includes, among other things, your: name; street or mailing address; telephone number(s); email addresses; date of birth; gender; nationality; purchases of products; payment information; credit card numbers; marketing preferences; answers you provide to security questions (such as your mother’s maiden name, the name of your pet, etc.); information used to provide products or services; information needed to administer rewards or loyalty programs, including transaction and correspondence details; and any other types of information that you choose to provide to us or that we may collect about you through your transactions with Daily Vanity, will be stored by and on Daily Vanity.
  3. When submitting your information via our forms, you will be informed on the party(ies) who will also be receiving the information you provided through that submission. If you do not agree to it, please do not submit. If none are mentioned that means only Daily Vanity will be receiving it.
  4. Information collected under Daily Vanity will be retained under the authority of DAILY VANITY Pte Ltd. In the event of a sale of any DAILY VANITY Pte Ltd’s asset including customer information, buyers will be required to honour our Privacy Policy or provide you a notice and option to limit the sharing of your information.
  5. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future email notifications, we have included an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

## PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

  1. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## USAGE OF COOKIES

  1. When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more “cookies.” By accessing our website, you agree that we can place cookies on your device.
  2. This website and third-party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to this website. Also, this information will be used to enhance your shopping experience.
  3. A cookie is a small text file that contains information that can later be read by us to facilitate your access to our website, gather statistical data, and personalize your online experience. We currently use cookies on our website for purposes including, but not limited to, detecting your web browser’s multimedia capabilities, tracking promotional advertisements that we have displayed to you, maintaining current login and providing a unique identifier to your computer so that we can generate statistics regarding website usage.
  4. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies. Generally, you can remove these cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.  If you choose not to allow us to place a cookie on your computer, you may be restricted from some services and some of the interactive features offered on our websites may be similarly restricted or rendered inoperable.
  5. In addition to cookies, we may also use other Internet technologies, such as web beacons or pixel tags, and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of our website. The information we obtain in this manner enables us measure the overall effectiveness of our online content, advertising campaigns, and the products we offer through our website. By accessing our website and agreeing to receive our e-mail messages or newsletters, you agree to that we can use other Internet technologies such as those mentioned above on your device(s).
  6. Our website may allow third parties to download cookies to your device(s). Third parties, such as Google Analytics, may use cookies and other technologies to collect non-personal data about your online activities while you are on our website. This information may be used to measure usage of our website and personalize advertising content on our website. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features these third parties may use, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  Please refer to the privacy policies of those third parties to better understand their activities and practices.

## THIRD PARTY LINKS

  1. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT

  1. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as these parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours and others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## OPT-OUT

  1. If you do not wish to receive any further information from Daily Vanity regarding newsletters, launches, offers, promotions from partners or special events via email, you may unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link in our mailers.
  2. Should you decide to have your information removed from the relevant third party(ies), you will need to contact them directly as Daily Vanity does not have the legal means to enact the removal process with any third party(ies).
  3. Please note that if you withdraw your consent for a limited purpose, such as for marketing, we may still contact you or use your information for other purposes for which you have not withdrawn your consent and such personal data may still be shared, as permitted under the PDPA and other applicable law.

## USAGE OF SITE

  1. DAILY VANITY may feature pictures, articles, information, digital images, text, data, games, surveys, contests, promotions, advertising, logos, trademarks and other forms of content*** we deem will be of interest to our customers or visitors. This Content can be viewed, transferred, shared and stored by our customers and guest. However, the ownership of this Content belongs to DAILY VANITY PTE LTD and by downloading or storing of this Content does not render the customer or visitor the rights nor ownership to it.
  2. ***Collectively, content composite one or more of the following – text, data, music, sound, graphics, images, pictures, photographs, videos, software or other forms later created or not known at this time.
  3. Content extracted from DailyVanity.com & DailyVanity.sg and published or shared on any platforms must be credited and linked back to the respective web pages. DAILY VANITY PTE LTD reserves the rights to pursue legal actions against unauthorized usage of this Content.

## SECURITY

  1. Daily Vanity practises reasonable precautions to protect your personal data and store it securely.  However, you should be aware that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage has 100% security. While security cannot be guaranteed, we strive to protect the security of your information and are constantly reviewing and enhancing our information security measures.  Daily Vanity’s website has security measures in place that strive to protect against the accidental loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information while under our control.  Such security measures include, but are not limited to, password controls, firewalls, and other industry standard security measures.

## PRIVACY POLICY AMENDMENTS

  1. Daily Vanity (DAILY VANITY PTE. LTD) reserves the rights to amend any of the policies above at any time.  The Effective Date, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was materially revised.  We encourage you to review this page periodically as changes may be made to our policy from time to time regarding the collection and use of your personal data.
  2. Your continued use of our website and acceptance of our services after any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to any such changes; to the extent such consent is not otherwise provided.

Last updated on 4 May 2018
